amigobulls.com 2018-12-29

# Privacy Policy, amigobulls.com

Please read the Privacy Policy & [Terms of Use](https://amigobulls.com/terms) before using our Website.

We are committed to protecting your privacy while you use our Website. The policy below (referred as "Privacy Policy") explains how we handle the information that we collect implicitly and explicitly from your activities on our site.

* * *

The Information that we collect and how we use:

WEB COOKIES

To serve you better, we install what are known as 'Web Cookies' on your system. This a standard mechanism supported by all web browsers and used by many a websites to store information about your usage of the website. Cookies are not 'active' programs that can run on your computer, they are textual information that gets stored by a browser on your computer or a mobile device. We do not use cookies to store any 'personal' information like 'passwords', your name, and address. Currently we use them to store your preferences about certain type of stocks, news, articles etc. This helps us in providing you with relevant content the next time you visit our site. We may use cookies to store certain identifiers that help us identify your browser. Apart from cookies installed by our site, our advertisers may install their own cookies to track your preference regarding advertisements. Currently we use Google Ad-Sense for serving ads on our Website, their privacy policy is listed at <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy> In future we may use other advertisers in addition to Google Ad-Sense. We will keep you informed about their privacy policy.

* * *

IP ADDRESS

IP address is another information that we receive when you access our Website. It helps us identify your location to certain degree. We and our advertising partners use this information to serve you relevant content.

* * *

DEVICE INFORMATION

We get to know about the device (a mobile device, a tablet or a computer) when you access our Website. We use this information to serve you content which is suitably formatted to your device. We may associate the device identifiers that we may receive with your other information.

* * *

PERSONAL INFORMTAION

We may ask you to submit your personal information like e-mail IDs, phone number, and address to use certain services on our Website. We may collect this information from other web-sites (like Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, and Google). Collection of such information will be done only with your explicit approval. We will use this information only for our internal use and to send you relevant information. We will not share this information with any of our partners including advertisers. We may share this information in a statistically non-identifiable way to inform potential advertisers, partners etc.

* * *

EMAIL & ALERTS: NON SPAMMING POLICY

We will not send you more than 2 emails per week without your explicit approval for more number of messages. We will always provide you an option to opt out of any such e-mails or alerts that you no longer wish to receive.

* * *

CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

Amigobulls reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy & Terms of Use, at any time. You should check the Website frequently to see recent changes. For any queries regarding our Privacy Policy or Terms of Use, contact us at [contact@amigobulls.com](mailto:contact@amigobulls.com)
